Register of the Jay Lovestone papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- PRINTED MATERIAL, 1911-1977 (Boxes 1-191)
  - Senat of Berlin Report, Refugees Flooding the Island of Berlin, 1953
  - Senate Republican Memo, 1961 June 29
  - Senator fur Inneres, Ostliche Untergrundarbeit gegen Westberlin, 1959
  - Senior, Clarence, Self-Determination for Puerto Rico, 1946
  - Senturia, Joseph J., Strikes, 1935
  - Serge, Victor, From Lenin to Stalin, 1937 (Box 141)
  - Service d'Archives (incomplete), 1938-1939
  - Service de Presse, 1969 April 28
  - Service d'Etudes et d'Information de la Federation Americaine du Travail, Comment vit l'ouvrier de presse americain, 1947
  - Service Hebdomadaire de Documentation Politique, Les informations politiques et sociales, 1968 June 6, 7, 8, 10
  - Der 17. Juni, der Tag der Volkserhebung, 1953
  - Shelepin, Alexander, Report of the All-Union Central Council of Trade Unions to the 15th Congress of Trade Unions of the USSR, 1972
  - Shevchenko, Taras, Europe's Freedom Fighter, 1960
  - Shibley, Fred W., The Banker's Relation to Industrial Reconstruction Since 1920, 1924
  - Shifrin, A., How Aliya Is Being Killed, 1975
  - Simmons, E. H. H., The Principal Causes of the Stock Market Crisis of Nineteen Twenty Nine, 1930
  - Sinclair, Upton
    - The Flivver King, 1937
    - Immediate Epic, circa 1934
    - We, People of America, circa 1934
  - Sinclair, Upton and Eugene Lyons, Terror in Russia? Two Views, 1938
  - Sindicalismo en Espana, 1972 November-December
  - Der Sinn des Zusammenbruchs!, 1930
  - The Sino-Indian Conflict, 1963
  - The Sino-Japanese Crisis, 1937
  - Slessor, J. C., Air Power and Armies, 1936
  - Smith, Bruch L. R., The Governance of Berlin, 1959
  - Smith, Edwin S., Organized Labor in the Soviet Union, 1943
  - Smith, Rennie, Peace Verboten, 1943
  - Smogorzewski, Casimir, About the Curzon Line and Other Lines, 1944
  - Smole, Joze, Yugoslav Views on Coexistence, 1961
  - Social Action, 1940 April 15, 1946 December 15 (Box 142)
  - Social Democrats, U.S.A.
    - America and the World Crisis, 1975
    - Bloodbath!, undated
  - The Social Economic Foundation, A Labor Party for the United States, 1936
  - Social Science Research Council
    - Research in Employer-Employee Relations in the Public Service, 1940
    - Studies in Administration, undated
  - Social Service Outlook, 1970 November
  - Socialism and Peace, 1936
  - Socialist Alternative for Eastern Europe, 1959
  - Socialist Appeal, 1936 October 1
  - Socialist Clarity Group, Discussion Notes (incomplete), 1939-1940, 1942
  - Socialist Commentary, 1956 February
  - Socialist Correspondence (incomplete), 1937-1939
  - Socialist International Information (incomplete), 1953-1968
  - Socialist Leader, 1951 January 6
  - Socialist Party, Bombay, Labour College, 1947 (Box 143)
  - Socialist Party of the United States
    - The Intelligent Voter's Guide, 1928
    - A Political Guide for the Workers, 1920
    - Socialist Hand Book, 1916
    - Towards a Militant Program for the Socialist Party of America, 1934
    - Unions Face the Depression, 1938
    - What Socialism Will Really Mean to You, undated
  - Le socialiste, 1965 March 25
  - Society for the Prevention of World War III, Press Digest, 1969 Fall
  - Sohns, Hansfritz, Kampf und Aufstieg des Nationalsozialismus zum Dritten Reich, 1933
  - Sohyo News (incomplete), 1953-1967
  - Sokolov, V. L., Soviet Use of German Science and Technology, 1945-1946, 1955
  - Solidaridad, 1941 April-May
  - Solidaritat, 1964 November, 1965 July
  - Solidarity, 1936 April
  - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr, Nobel Lecture, 1973
  - Some Facts and Figures about the United States, 1959
  - Sonne, H. Christian, Our Achilles Heel: World Liquidity, 1967
  - Sonter, R., Der neue deutsche Imperialismus, 1928
  - Souchy, Augustin, The Tragic Week in May, 1937 (Box 144)
  - Soule, George, The Accumulation of Capital, 1924
  - Source List of International Relations Materials, 1969-1970, undated
  - Sources of Power in the U.S.S.R., 1958
  - Soustelle, Jacques, The Wealth of the Sahara, 1959
  - South Africa Information Service, The Truth that Hurts, 1961
  - South Viet Nam in Struggle, 1972 May 8
  - South Viet Nam National Front for Liberation, Documents, 1968
  - Southeast Asian Perspectives, 1971 December
  - Soviet Analyst, 1973 January 4, February 1
  - Soviet and Communist Attitudes Toward Islam, undated
  - Soviet Periodical Abstracts, 1962 October, December
  - Soviet Plan and Budget: 1974
  - Soviet Survey, 1958 October-December, 1959 January-March, October-December, 1960 October-December
  - Soviet Trade Unions, 1917-1967
  - Soviet World Outlook, 1976 June 15
  - The Sower Press, The Catholic Worker Stand on Strikes, 1938
  - Sozial-okonomische Arbeiter-Rundschau, 1928 September
  - Sozialistische Arbeiter Bibliothek, Die Internationale in Amerika, 1918
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands
    - Auslandsbrief (incomplete), 1955-1968 (Box 145)
    - Basic Programme of the Social Democratic Party of Germany, 1959
    - Bonner, Depesche, 1963 January
    - Deutschland Plan der SPD, 1959
    - Dokumentation der Unmenschlichkeit gegenuber Deutschen..., undated
    - Entschliessungen des SPD-Parteitages in Saarbrucken, 1970
    - Germany, Monthly Reports (incomplete), 1939-1940
    - International Socialist Conference, 1950
    - Die Neuordnung Deutschlands, 1956
    - Pressedienst, 1962 March 28, April 17, 27
    - Protokoll, SPD Parteitag Hannover, 1960 November (Box 146)
    - Querschnitt durch Politik und Wirtschaft, March 1950
    - Remers trojanische Pferde, undated
    - Ruhr Statute and Security, undated
    - Sopade Informationsdienst, 1948 April
    - Tatsachen - Argumente, 1967
    - Wie die Sowjets URAN gewinnen, undated
    - Willy Brandt antwortet, undated
    - Wir und der Vietnam-Konflikt, undated
    - Wort gehalten, 1969
  - Sozialpolitischer Ausschuss des ADGB, Die Sozialrenten, undated
  - Spaethen, Rolf, Was hat der Westen dem Kommunismus entgegenzusetzen?, undated
  - Spain
    - Buenaventura Durruti, 1936
    - Report on Higher Education in Spain, undated
    - Spain, undated
    - Spain-Anarchism, undated
  - Spain Today, 1962 June
  - Spanish Committee on Liberation, Appeal to the San Francisco Conference, 1945 April
  - Spanish Newsletter, 1968 December 31
  - The Spanish Revolution (incomplete), 1937 January-April
  - Spanish Workers' Party of Marxist Unity, A Lead to World Socialism, 1936
  - Spartacist, 1968 May, September-October
  - Spartacus, 1937 May, 1939 June
  - Special Information Note, 1964 April 1, 3
  - Special Survey Reports, 1956 July-August
  - The Spectator, 1931 September 26, 1961 May 5
  - Spectator Germaniae, Hindenburg in Wahlkampf, 1925-1932, undated
  - Spingarn, Jerome, H., New Approaches to Disarmament, 1962
  - Spiro, Jacob S., and John Milton, Gist of the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1941
  - The Spivack Report (incomplete), 1967-1970 (Box 147)
  - Spotlight, 1965 July
  - Spotlight on Africa, 1968 May
  - Sprague, Robert C., ABM--Deterrence and the Impact of a Technical Breakthrough in the Nuclear Age, 1969
  - Spratt, Philip
    - The Communist Peace Appeal, 1951
    - Morality and Political Practice, 1948
  - Sprecher, William M., World-Wide Defense Expenditures and Selected Economic Data, 1964, 1966
  - Sprenger, Rudolf, Bolshevism, undated
  - Staatsburgerliche Informationen, 1958 October
  - Stajner, R., Distribution of Income in Enterprises, 1961
  - Stalin, Joseph
    - Building Collective Farms, 1931
    - Fragen und Antworten, 1925
    - Der Oppositionsblock und die Fragen der Revolution in der UdSSR, 1927
    - Politischer Bericht des Zentralkomitees an den 16. arteitag der KPdSU, 1930
    - Questions & Answers to American Trade Unionists, 1927
    - The Road to Power, 1937
    - Speech at an Election Rally in Stalin Electoral Area, 1946 February 9
    - Stalin's Speeches on the American Communist Party, 1929
    - The Theory and Practice of Leninism, 1925
    - Unterrendung mit der Ersten, 1927
  - Stamp, L. Dudley, The Face of Britain, 1940
  - The Standing Committee on Education about Communism and Its Contrast with Liberty under Law, Liberty under Law Anarchy Totalitarianism--This Is the Choice, 1969
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), Research for Industry, 1962 September-October
  - Stanley, Timothy W., A Conference on European Security?, 1970
  - Star, 1971 September 1 (Box 148)
  - Stark, J., Zentrumsherrschaft und Jesuitenpolitik, 1932
  - Stark, Johannes, Adolf Hitlers Ziele und Personlichkeit, 1932
  - Starobin, J., Viet-Nam Fights for Freedom, 1953
  - Starr, Mark, Labour Politics in the U.S.A, 1949
  - Steel Labor, 1943 January 30
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee
    - Industrial Training, undated
    - Organized Labor and Management, undated
    - Production Problems, undated
  - Steibel, Gerald L.
    - Detente: Dilemma or Disaster?, 1969
    - How Can We Negotiate with the Communists?, 1972
  - Steinbuch, Pladoyer fur eine liberale Zukunft, 1975
  - Sternberg, Fritz, In Order to Survive, 1941
  - Stevenson, Adlai E.
    - Red China and the United Nations, 1961
    - Survival & Freedom, undated
  - Stewart, Maxwell S.
    - America's Factories, 1941
    - Debts--Good or Bad?, 1939
    - How Shall We Pay for Defense?, 1941
    - How We Spend Our Money, 1938
    - Industrial Price Policies, 1938
    - A New Look at Our Crowded World, 1966
    - Our Taxes--And What They Buy, 1939
    - Readjustments Required for Recovery, 1937
    - Saving Our Soil, 1937
    - Security or the Dole?, 1938
    - Steel--Problems of a Great Industry, 1937
    - That No Man Shall Hunger!, 1960
    - Youth in the World of Today, 1938
  - Stimme der Freiheit, 1955 April-May
  - Stimmen aus Deutschland, 1940 February
  - Stimson, Henry, The Challenge to Americans, 1947
  - Stoedtner, Gerhard, Frieden Wiedervereinigung Sicherheit, 1959
  - Stoessinger, John G., Financing the United Nations, 1961
  - Stolz, Otto, Wenn zwei das Gleiche tun..., 1952
  - Stone, William T., America Rearms, 1941
  - Stone, William T., and Ryllis Alexander Goslin, Billions for Defense, 1937
  - Strachey, John, The Pursuit of Peace, 1960
  - Strategic Review, 1975 Fall (Box 149)
  - Streit, Clarence K., Where Iron Is, There Is the Fatherland!, 1920
  - Strike Newspaper, Yale University, 1970 April 27
  - Strong, Anna Louise, The Rise of the Chinese People's Communes, 1959
  - The Struggle in Spain, 1937
  - Strzelwica, W., Die russische Revolution und der Sozialismus, 1956
  - Student Unrest in Eastern Europe, 1969
  - Studies on the Soviet Union, 1962
  - Sturm, Organ der revolutionaren SA der Saar, undated
  - Sturmthal, Adolf, The Workers' Councils in Poland, 1961
  - Sullivan, John, The Reform of the Rating System, 1939
  - Sullivan, William C., Freedom Is the Exception, 1965
  - Summaries of Selected Japanese Magazines, 1964 November 2, 9
  - Summary of Labor Press, 1960 November-December, 1961 February-March
  - Summit County Labor News, 1942 January 23
  - Summit Diplomacy, 1958 October
  - Supreme Court of the United States, Communist Party of the United States of America, Petitioner, v. Subversive Activities Control Board, 1961 June 5
  - Survey, 1963 April, 1968 July
  - Survey of China Mainland Press (incomplete), 1954-1968 (Box 150)
  - Survival, 1965 January-February, 1966 November (Box 151)
  - Sweden
    - Labor Peace and Full Employment in Sweden, 1964
    - Social Benefits in Sweden, 1962
  - Swiss Review of World Affairs (incomplete), 1958-1976
  - Sword over Europe, undated (Box 152)
  - Syme, Adjingboru A., Ghanaians Salute Israel, 1958
  - Symes, Lillian
    - Communism--World Revolution to Red Imperialism, undated
    - Our American Dreyfus Case: A Challenge to California Justice, 1935
  - Le syndicaliste exile, 1951 February, May, December, 1965 October, 1966 July
  - Syndicalisme, 1968 June 10
  - Sztaray, Zoltan, Two Books on the Hungarian Revolution, 1960
  - Szulc, Tad, News Trends in Latin America, 1960
  - Szumski, Romuald, Labor and the Soviet System, undated
  - T.G. Masaryk, Champion of Liberty, 1960
  - TUCSA Newsletter, 1964 May, 1965 June
  - The Tablet, South America Reds Plan Overthrow of the Church, 1944
  - Tactics, 1971 May 20
  - Taft, Philip
    - The Bisbee Deportation, 1972
    - On the Origins of Business Unionism, 1963
    - The Responses of the Bakers, Longshoremen and Teamsters to Public Exposure, 1960
  - Tamiment Institute Public Forum, Is Co-Existence Possible?, 1955
  - Tanganyika
    - Address by His Excellency the Governor to Legislative Council, 1957 September 17
    - Sauti Ya Tanu, 1958 February 13
  - Tanganyika Federation of Labour, Trade Union Suppression in Sisal Industry, 1957 September 28
  - Tannous, Izzat
    - The Expulsion of the Palestine Arabs from Their Homeland, 1961
    - Failures of the United Nations in the Palestine Tragedy, 1959
    - Towards Better Understanding between the Arab World and the United States, 1960
  - Tasks for the Free World Today, 1964
  - Tast, E., Ce que l'on vous cache, undated
  - Taylor, Paul S., Adrift on the Land, 1940
  - Taylor, Wayne Chatfield, The Firestone Operations in Liberia, 1956
  - Technology and the American Economy, 1966 February
  - Tele-Control, 1972 October
  - Terre Haute Advocate, 1942 January 23
  - Terre Nouvelle, 1936 June
  - Terry, J. William, American Labor and the Trade Agreements, 1939
  - Textile, 1974 Spring
  - Thalheimer, August (Lambda)
    - On Dialectics, 1933
    - The Truth about the Barcelona Events, 1937
  - The "Thaw" in Eastern Europe, 1966 June
  - Thiokol Chemical Corporation, 1958 Annual Report, 1959
  - Thomas, Norman (Box 153)
    - Democracy versus Dictatorship, 1937
    - The Plight of the Share-Cropper, 1934
  - Thomson, George G., Problems of Strategy in the Pacific and Indian Oceans, 1970
  - Thought (incomplete), 1953-1970
  - 338 News, 1941 February (Box 154)
  - Thude, Guenter, The Workers and Their Social Insurance, 1961
  - Tibet: A Few Facts, Committee for Solidarity with Tibet, undated
  - The Times, The Dollar Gap, 1949
  - Tisma, Tosa, Management of Social Property, 1961
  - Tito, Josip Broz
    - President Tito's Visit to Friendly African Countries, 1961
    - Speech by President Josip Broz-Tito, 1961
    - With Friends in Africa, 1961
  - Today in France, 1966 October, December, 1967 January, February
  - Together, The Atlantic Union Bulletin, 1974 June
  - Toledano, Nora de, Time Marches on McCarthy, 1952 February
  - Tong Cong Doan Viet-Nam, 1965 November 22, 1966 January 6
  - Topalovich, Zivko, Les usines aux ouvriers, 1952
  - Tractor AFL Worker, 1942 January 22
  - Trade and Aid to the Developing Countries, 1971
  - The Trades Union Congress
    - Agenda of the 1957 Congress
    - Agenda for the 1971 Congress
    - Free Trade Unions leave the W.F.T.U., 1949
    - Interim Report on Public Ownership, 1953
    - 1952 Congress
    - Preliminary Agenda and Final Notice of Annual Congress, 1968
    - The Trades Union Congress, 1962
    - Trades Union Congress Economic Review, 1970
    - What the TUC Is Doing, 1951 Spring, 1952-1953
  - Trade Union Correspondence, 1968 April 15, 1970 April 5, 1976 July
  - Trade Union Council of South Africa, Why TUCSA Opposes Boycotts and Sanctions, undated
  - The Trade Union Educational League
    - Needle Trades Left Wing Program, 1926
    - Trade Unions in America, undated
  - Trade Union News Bulletin from Norway, 1967 June
  - Trade Union Press, 1961-1970 (Box 155)
  - Trade Unions, undated
  - Trade Unions and Productivity, undated
  - Trade Unions in Sweden, 1961
  - Trade Unions of Romania, 1969
  - Trade Winds, 1929 February
  - Trans-Atlantic, 1948 September
  - Transinformations, 1968 June
  - Translations from Kommunist
    - 1972
    - 1973-1974 (Box 156)
  - Transport & General Workers' Union, Chairman's Address, 1953 July (Box 157)
  - The Treaty of August 12, 1970 between the Federal Republic of Germany and the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics
  - Trends of Communist Propaganda (incomplete), 1961-1962
  - Trezise, Philip H., Our Two Countries, 1972
  - The Trial of Freedom, 1962
  - Tribune, 1941 December 19, 1943 October 8, 1946 August 23
  - Trotskii, Lev (Box 158)
    - The Draft Program of the Communist International, 1929
    - From October to Brest Litovsk, 1919
    - Die neue Etappe, 1921
    - The Soviet Union and the Fourth International, 1934
  - Trumbull, Robert, India since Independence, 1954
  - Tsamerian, I. P., and S. L. Ronin, Equality of Rights between Races and Nationalities in the USSR, 1962
  - Tsiang, Tingfu F., The Charter of the United Nations and the Package Deal, 1955
  - Tunisia, Aspects de la vie sociale tunisienne, 1957
  - Turk-Is News Bulletin, 1977 May-June
  - The Twentieth Century (incomplete), 1952-1960
  - Two Months of Malenkov, 1953
  - U.D.A. (Union for Democratic Action) (Box 159)
    - Action Leaflet No. 2, Stop Price Rises Now!, undated
    - London Letter (incomplete), 1950
  - UE (United Electrical), Radio and Machine Workers of America
    - All of Us Built America, 1968
    - How Foreign is "Foreign" Competition, undated
    - UE News, 1946 October 5
  - UNESCO, Educational Studies and Documents, New Trends in Youth Organizations, 1960
  - U.S.A., 1958 February 28
  - USDAW Visits Russia, Shops and Catering in the U.S.S.R., undated
  - USSR Exhibition, New York, 1959
  - Uganda Peoples Congress, Policy Statement, 1960 December
  - Ukraine Farming and Machinery Corporation, undated
  - The Ukrainian Bulletin (incomplete), 1955-1961
  - The Ukrainian Quarterly, 1960 Spring
  - Ulbricht: A Danger to Peace, undated
  - Ulmer, Hans, Wollen wir den Klassenkampf?, 1973
  - Umoh, Umoh James, Before Darkness Falls, undated
  - Uncensored, 1941 March 29, July 12
  - Union, Organ of the Philippine Civic Union, 1941 March 15
  - Union General De Trabajadores, Boletin, 1949 September
  - l'Union Generale des Travailleurs d'Afrique Noire, Resolutions, 1959 January
  - Union Herald, 1962 April
  - Union of Democratic Control
    - Patriotism, Ltd., 1933
    - The Secret International, 1934
  - Union Research Service
    - 1955
    - 1956 (Box 160)
  - United Asia (incomplete), 1959-1960 (Box 161)
  - United Automobile Workers of America
    - Agreements, 1937
    - Constitution, 1966 May, 1970 April
    - Ford Facts, 1970 April 13
    - Miscellaneous
    - News from UAW, 1968 July 23, 1970 October 23
    - Public Review Board, 1971
    - Reports and Resolutions (incomplete), 1957-1972
    - Sane, 1971 Eleanor Roosevelt Peace Award
    - Solidar Report, 1965 May-June
    - UAW Administrative Letter, 1956 May 21, 1966 August 29, 1967 August 1 (Box 162)
    - UAW Solidarity, 1960 June, 1962 January
    - United Automobile Worker, 1937 December 18, 1956 March
  - United Construction Workers Organizing Committee, Rules and Regulations, 1939 August 1
  - The United Farmer, 1928 May 16
  - United Farmers' Educational League, Statement, undated
  - The United Front that Failed, 1966
  - United Kingdom Council of the European Movement, Summary of Reports, 1949 April
  - United Kingdom Overseas Investments, 1938 to 1948, 1950
  - United Labor Conference, Equal Sacrifice for the Defense of America, 1951 March
  - United Mine Workers of America, Minutes, reports, and resolutions of the Thirtieth Consecutive Constitutional Convention, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1927
  - United Nations
    - Agreement Establishing the Asian Development Bank, 1965
    - Agricultural Mechanization, 1959
    - Charter of the United Nations and Statute of the International Court of Justice, 1963
    - China, the United Nations and United States Policy, 1966
    - The Chronicle of United Nations Activities, 1955 December 23
    - The Economic and Social Consequences for Disarmament, 1961
    - General Assembly minutes
      - 1945-1957
      - 1958-1973 (Box 163)
    - Index to the United Nations Review, 1958 July - 1959 June
    - Introduction to the Report of the Secretary-General on the Work of the Organization, 1973
    - Miscellaneous
    - Press Services, 1965 February 24 (Box 164)
    - A Program on United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation, 1944
    - Report of the International Law Commission, 1949
    - Report of the Secretary-General on the Work of the Organization, 1973
    - Restrictive Business Practices, 1972
    - Security Council, Statement by the Soviet Government on Cuba, 1962 October 23
    - Technical Assistance Committee, 1959
    - Tenth Anniversary of the Signing of the United Nations Charter, 1955
    - Toward the Reconciliation of Europe, 1969
    - UNRRA, Organization, Aims, Progress, 1944
    - The United Nations: What You Should Know About It, 1957
    - United Nations Work for Human Rights, 1961
    - United Nations Trade and Development Conference, 1964
  - The United Nations, 1946 March 1, April 1
  - The United Nations and Red China, circa 1967
  - United Shoe and Leather Workers Union, For Better Wages, Hours and Conditions, Organize!, undated
  - United States
    - Advisory Commission on International Educational and Cultural Affairs, International Educational and Cultural Exchange, 1966 (Box 165)
    - Agency for International Development
      - An Act for International Development, 1961
      - Information Bulletin, 1971 June
      - The Other War in South Vietnam, 1965
      - Primer on Title IX, 1969
      - U.S. Foreign Aid and the Alliance for Progress, 1969
      - U.S. Foreign Aid in East Asia, 1969
      - Why Foreign Aid, undated
    - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency
      - Agenda Item-Peace, 1964
      - Arms Control and National Security, 1970
      - Review of International Negotiations on the Cessation of Nuclear Weapon Tests, 1966
      - World Military Expenditures, 1969-1970
    - Central Intelligence Agency, Soviet Manpower, 1960-1970
    - Congress
      - Joint Economic Committee
        - American Productivity: Key to Economic Strength and National Survival, 1972
        - Automation and Technology in Education, 1966
        - Comparisons of the United States and Soviet Economies, Parts I, II, III, 1959
        - Economic Aspects of Military Procurement and Supply, 1960
        - Economic Policies and Practices, 1963
        - Economic Programs for Labor Surplus Areas in Selected Countries of Western Europe, 1960
        - Hearings, 1963 July 29-30
        - A New Initiative to Liberalize International Trade, 1973
        - A New Look at Trade Policy Toward the Communist Bloc, 1961
        - Notes, 1975 July 1
        - Subsidy and Subsidylike Programs of the U.S. Government, 1960
      - Public Law 831, International Security Law, 1950
      - House (Box 166)
        - Bills
          - H.R. 9546, 1921 December 14
          - H.R. 3471, 1935 January 9
        - Committee on Appropriations
          - Departments of State, Justice and Commerce, the Judiciary, and Related Agencies Appropriations for 1971, 1970
          - Safeguard Antiballistic Missile System, 1969
        - Committee on Foreign Affairs
          - Membership and Participation by the United States in the United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization, 1946
          - National and International Political Movements, 1947
          - Plants and Part Plants, 1947
          - Tension and Detente: Congressional Perspectives on Soviet-American Relations, 1973
          - United States Policy Toward Asia, 1966
        - Committee on Un-American Activities
          - The Communist Conspiracy, 1956
          - Communist Infiltration of Vital Industries and Current Communist Techniques in the Chicago, Ill. Area, 1959
          - The Crimes of Khrushchev, 1959
          - Documentary Testimony of Gen. Izyador Modelski, 1949
          - Hearings on American Aspects of the Richard Sorge Spy Case, 1951
          - International Communism, 1957